<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SeaX Messaging on </title>
    <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SeaX Messaging on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bulk SMS</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/bulk-messaging-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/bulk-messaging-features/</guid>
      <description>Overview #  The Bulk Messaging Platform puts all the tools you need for SMS and MMS marketing together in one convenient platform. On the Bulk Messaging Platform, you can:
Send
 Send bulk SMS and MMS messages Send now or schedule messages up to 7 days in advance Automatically filter &amp;lsquo;Do Not Contact&amp;rsquo; customers out of send lists View delivery reports on bulk messaging waves Send messages from multiple phone numbers  Receive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Business</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-whatsapp-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-whatsapp-integration/</guid>
      <description>SeaX Messaging supports WhatsApp integration, allowing you to connect with your customers on WhatsApp. This guide will walk you through the steps to integrate WhatsApp with SeaX Messaging. Start leveraging the power of SeaX Messaging to engage with your customers on WhatsApp today!
 Connect WhatsApp with SeaX Messaging # Head to Channels under Workspace in the sidebar menu. Click on WhatsApp Business App to start the integration process.
   Click on WhatsApp Business App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeaX Widget</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-widget/</guid>
      <description>Overview # In this article, we will introduce the SeaX Widget, a feature of the SeaX Messaging platform that allows you to integrate a widget button that your customers can click on and directly send a message to your SeaX Messaging account. You will learn how you can set up the SeaX Widget and integrate it into your website or app.
 Why SeaX Widget? # Providing a seamless experience for your customers is crucial for any business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeaX Bulk Send/Call with SeaChat</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-agent-bulk-send/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-agent-bulk-send/</guid>
      <description>SeaX Bulk Send/Call with SeaChat # SeaX bulk messaging offers a powerful way to manage communications across multiple business channels from a single platform. With SeaX, you can not only send messages to different customers but also automate these conversations by integrating with SeaChat.
This guide will walk you through the process of sending bulk messages and calls using SeaX and SeaChat, helping you streamline your business communication.
Set Up Workspace # To integrate SeaX with SeaChat, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a phone number to send messages and an AI agent to handle the conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Features &amp; Releases</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-messaging-product-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seax/seax_messaging/seax-messaging-product-updates/</guid>
      <description>09/12/2024 # New Features and Performance Optimization #  Added the &amp;ldquo;Business Caller ID&amp;rdquo; binding feature, allowing purchased numbers to be linked with verified &amp;ldquo;Business Caller IDs&amp;rdquo; for outbound calls. Introduced dynamic loading for WhatsApp messages to improve overall loading efficiency and user experience. Added a history log for purchased numbers. Conversations with deleted contacts are retained and linked when contacts are re-added.  Bugfix #  Fixed the issue where AI agents failed to handle incoming calls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
