<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seasalt RESTful APIs Documentation on </title>
    <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seasalt RESTful APIs Documentation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SeaChat API</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/01-seachat-api-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/01-seachat-api-intro/</guid>
      <description>This feature is only available on 
Enterprise  Premium  plans 
 SeaChat RESTful API allows users to integrate and automate chatbot workflows, providing the flexibility to manage AI agents programmatically. By utilizing the API, users can incorporate chatbot capabilities into their own applications or systems. The API documentation offers detailed information and guidance for seamless integration.
SeaChat API Docs   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeaX API</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/02-seax-api-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/02-seax-api-intro/</guid>
      <description>This feature is only available on 
Enterprise  Premium  plans 
 SeaX Messaging API allows users to integrate and automate messaging workflows, providing the flexibility to manage campaigns programmatically. By utilizing the API, users can incorporate messaging capabilities into their own applications or systems, streamlining operations, automating processes, and efficiently scaling messaging efforts. The API documentation offers detailed information and guidance for seamless integration, and users can obtain their API key from the &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; tab to securely access the API functionalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeaMeet API</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/03-seameet-api-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seasaltapi/seasalt-api/03-seameet-api-intro/</guid>
      <description>This feature is only available on 
Enterprise  Premium  plans 
 Unlock the full potential of video conferencing with the SeaMeet API from SeaSalt. Designed for seamless integration, this API empowers developers to automate and manage video meetings with ease. Key features include automated meeting transcription, recording, and sharing, all of which streamline your conferencing needs. This comprehensive documentation provides detailed guides and references, ensuring developers can implement the API efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
