<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SeaMeet User Guide on </title>
    <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SeaMeet User Guide on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Use SeaMeet Copilot</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/01-seameet-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/01-seameet-intro/</guid>
      <description>You can invite the SeaMeet Copilot to join and take notes of your Google Meet meetings in three different ways:
&amp;ldquo;Start Recording&amp;rdquo; from the Meeting List #  Click the &amp;lsquo;Start Recording&amp;rsquo; button. Enter the Google Meet code and submit. The meeting will automatically be added to your meeting list.   Invite via SeaMeet Chrome Extension #  Install the SeaMeet extension from the Chrome Web Store. Once installed, open Google Meet, and the extension will activate automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Subscribe to a Plan</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/en/seameet/manual/subscription/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/en/seameet/manual/subscription/</guid>
      <description>1. Register and Log In to SeaMeet # Log in to SeaMeet and start using it immediately. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t registered yet, please refer to here to register.
2. Plans and Billing # After logging in, find and click on the Billing page in the left menu.
  3. Edit Plan # Enter the &amp;ldquo;Plans&amp;rdquo; page and click the Edit Plan button to view available subscription plans.
  4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billing and Subscription</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/billing-and-subscription/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/billing-and-subscription/</guid>
      <description>You can find all the information about billing and subscription in the billing section of the SeaMeet dashboard. Find Billing in the left sidebar of the dashboard.
   Billing and Subscription
 Subscription Plan # In the Plan section, you can see the details of your current subscription plan. Edit your plan by clicking the Edit Plan button.
Billing Details # Click on Cost Breakdown under Next Billing Period to see the details of your next billing details according to your subscription and usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/00-seameet-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/00-seameet-faq/</guid>
      <description>1. How do I start meeting transcription? # You can invite the SeaMeet Copilot to join the meeting in Google Calendar or Google Meet. Once the meeting starts, the Copilot will automatically join and begin transcription.
2. Which meeting platforms does SeaMeet support? # Currently, SeaMeet supports transcribing meetings held in Google Meet. More meeting platforms will be supported in the future.
3. Which languages does SeaMeet support? # SeaMeet currently supports transcribing meetings in Chinese and English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provide Feedback</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/15-seameet-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/15-seameet-help/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions about how to operate, you can always click on the How to Use section in the bottom left corner of SeaMeet to view instructional articles and videos in the manual.
Have More Questions? Want to Provide Feedback? # If you want to provide feedback, you can select the &amp;ldquo;Feedback&amp;rdquo; page from the left sidebar in SeaMeet and send an email to &amp;lt;email: seameet@seasalt.ai&amp;gt; explaining your needs or issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
