<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SeaMeet User Guide on </title>
    <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SeaMeet User Guide on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Record Google Meet Meetings</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/01-seameet-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/01-seameet-intro/</guid>
      <description>You can invite the SeaMeet Copilot to join and take notes of your Google Meet meetings in three different ways:
&amp;ldquo;Start Recording&amp;rdquo; from the Meeting List #  Click the &amp;lsquo;Start Recording&amp;rsquo; button. Enter the Google Meet code and submit. The meeting will automatically be added to your meeting list.   Invite via SeaMeet Chrome Extension #  Install the SeaMeet extension from the Chrome Web Store. Once installed, open Google Meet, and the extension will activate automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Subscribe to a Plan</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/en/seameet/manual/subscription/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/en/seameet/manual/subscription/</guid>
      <description>1. Register and Log In to SeaMeet # Log in to SeaMeet and start using it immediately. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t registered yet, please refer to here to register.
2. Plans and Billing # After logging in, find and click on the Billing page in the left menu.
  3. Edit Plan # Enter the &amp;ldquo;Plans&amp;rdquo; page and click the Edit Plan button to view available subscription plans.
  4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billing and Subscription</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/billing-and-subscription/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/billing-and-subscription/</guid>
      <description>You can find all the information about billing and subscription in the billing section of the SeaMeet dashboard. Find Billing in the left sidebar of the dashboard.
   Billing and Subscription
 Subscription Plan # In the Plan section, you can see the details of your current subscription plan. Edit your plan by clicking the Edit Plan button.
Billing Details # Click on Cost Breakdown under Next Billing Period to see the details of your next billing details according to your subscription and usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/00-seameet-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/00-seameet-faq/</guid>
      <description>1. What types of meeting recordings and platforms does SeaMeet support? # SeaMeet supports three ways of recording different meeting formats, including:
 Real-time recording for Google Meet Real-time recording for Microsoft Teams Audio file uploads  More online meeting platforms will be supported in the future.
2. How do I start recording a Google Meet session with SeaMeet? # You have several ways to invite the SeaMeet bot to join your Google Meet and record:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provide Feedback</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/15-seameet-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/15-seameet-help/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions about how to operate, you can always click on the How to Use section in the bottom left corner of SeaMeet to view instructional articles and videos in the manual.
Have More Questions? Want to Provide Feedback? # If you want to provide feedback, you can select the &amp;ldquo;Feedback&amp;rdquo; page from the left sidebar in SeaMeet and send an email to &amp;lt;email: seameet@seasalt.ai&amp;gt; explaining your needs or issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/new_drip_campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/new_drip_campaign/</guid>
      <description>SeaMeet New User Onboarding Drip Campaign # This drip campaign is designed to onboard new SeaMeet users, guiding them from initial sign-up to becoming power users. Each email is crafted to be engaging, informative, and visually appealing, with clear calls to action.
 Email 1: Welcome &amp;amp; Your First Recording #  Subject: Welcome to SeaMeet! Your first AI meeting assistant awaits 🚀 Goal: Get the user to record their first meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/seameet-drip-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/seameet-drip-campaign/</guid>
      <description>SeaMeet User Onboarding Drip Campaign # Campaign Overview # This drip campaign is designed to guide new SeaMeet users through a progressive onboarding journey, helping them discover and adopt key features while maximizing their meeting productivity. The campaign spans 6 weeks with 12 targeted touchpoints.
Campaign Goals #  Primary: Increase user activation and feature adoption Secondary: Reduce churn and increase subscription conversion Tertiary: Build user confidence and establish meeting recording habits  Target Audience # New SeaMeet users who have:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/seameet_drip_campaign_strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/seameet_drip_campaign_strategy/</guid>
      <description>SeaMeet User Onboarding Drip Campaign Strategy # Campaign Overview # This drip campaign is designed to guide new SeaMeet users through their first 30 days, ensuring they understand key features, experience quick wins, and develop lasting usage habits. The campaign focuses on progressive value delivery and feature adoption.
Target Audience #  New users who have signed up for SeaMeet Users who may have attended their first few meetings Both individual and team plan subscribers  Campaign Goals #  Reduce time-to-value: Help users record their first meeting within 48 hours Increase feature adoption: Ensure users discover and use core features Build habit formation: Establish regular usage patterns Prevent churn: Address common pain points proactively Drive upgrades: Showcase premium features for trial users   Email Sequence (30-Day Campaign) # Day 0: Welcome &amp;amp; Quick Start (Trigger: Account Creation) # Subject: &amp;ldquo;Welcome to SeaMeet!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
