<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SeaMeet User Guide on</title><link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/</link><description>Recent content in SeaMeet User Guide on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/0-browser-extension/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/0-browser-extension/</guid><description>SeaMeet is an easy-to-use meeting AI copilot that helps you transcribe, record, and analyze your meetings in REAL TIME.
We recommend taking the first step by installing our browser extension so you will always have SeaMeet on your side in meetings:
Install SeaMeet Extension</description></item><item><title>How to Use SeaMeet Copilot</title><link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/1-how-to-use-seameet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/1-how-to-use-seameet/</guid><description>You can invite the SeaMeet Copilot to join and take notes of your Google Meet meetings in three different ways:
&amp;ldquo;Start Recording&amp;rdquo; from the Meeting List # Click the &amp;lsquo;Start Recording&amp;rsquo; button. Enter the Google Meet code and submit. The meeting will automatically be added to your meeting list. Invite via SeaMeet Chrome Extension # Install the SeaMeet extension from the Chrome Web Store. Once installed, open Google Meet, and the extension will activate automatically.</description></item><item><title>View Meeting</title><link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-check-meeting-min/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-check-meeting-min/</guid><description>When you invite the SeaMeet Copilot to join a meeting, it will create a meeting entry in your workspace&amp;rsquo;s meeting list. Click on the meeting title to access detailed meeting information, including meeting transcription, discussed topics, summary, and action items.</description></item><item><title>Team Workspace Management</title><link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/4-seameet-workspace-management/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/4-seameet-workspace-management/</guid><description>About Workspace on Team Plan # If your organization purchased SeaMeet Team Plan, the workspace owner (the user account that created the first workspace) can create multiple workspaces and manage users on SeaMeet.
Workspace Owner # The user account that creates the workspace will be considered Workspace Owner, and the subscribed plan will apply to all workspaces under their administration.
If your team has multiple workspaces and you wish to use one subscription for all of them, please ensure that the workspace owner creates all the workspaces.</description></item><item><title>Track Meeting Performance</title><link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/3-track-meeting-performance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/3-track-meeting-performance/</guid><description>View statistics and analytics of your workspace meetings through the SeaMeet Performance Dashboard. SeaMeet Performance Dashboard is an advanced feature, please contact us at &amp;lt; email: seameet@seasalt.ai &amp;gt; if you are interested.</description></item></channel></rss>