<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General Setup on </title>
    <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General Setup on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Switch Meeting Language</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/08-seameet-language-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/08-seameet-language-setting/</guid>
      <description>SeaMeet currently supports three modes: Traditional Chinese, English, and automatic language detection. You can switch the meeting record language at any time before or during the meeting.
Switch Default Transcription Language #  Go to the Account -&amp;gt; Preference page. Set the default meeting recording language for your account for future invitations to the copilot. When starting a &amp;ldquo;Scheduled Meeting&amp;rdquo; recording, you will see that the default recording language has changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Share Meeting Records</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/10-seameet-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/10-seameet-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Get Started # You can adjust the recipients of automatically shared meeting records in the General of the Workspace.
   Auto Share Settings
  You can set the auto-sharing feature in the General. Currently, SeaMeet offers the following options:
  Only share with me
When you invite the copilot to transcribe a meeting, the system will automatically send an email to your inbox once the meeting ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcribe Meetings</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/03-seameet-how-to-invite-seameet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/03-seameet-how-to-invite-seameet/</guid>
      <description>Invite SeaMeet Copilot to Transcribe Meetings # SeaMeet is an AI tool that automatically generates meeting transcripts by inviting the copilot into the meeting room. Currently, SeaMeet mainly supports the Google Meet platform. SeaMeet supports multiple invitation methods, and you can choose one of the following three methods to invite the copilot:
1. Workspace Invitation #  Click the Start Recording button. Enter the Google Meet meeting code and submit. The meeting will automatically be added to the meeting list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Join Meetings</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/16-seameet-auto-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/16-seameet-auto-join/</guid>
      <description>Let SeaMeet automatically join your meetings without the need to manually enter the meeting ID and start a new meeting record. You can enable the auto-join feature in SeaMeet settings, and it will automatically join at the start of the meeting.
Sync with Google Calendar #  Go to the SeaMeet settings page, click Integration, and connect SeaMeet to the Google account you want.     1. SeaMeet Interface – Integration</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identify Speakers in In-Person Meetings</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/seameet-in-person-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seameet/seameet-manual/2-general-setup/seameet-in-person-meeting/</guid>
      <description>When recording in-person meetings using Google Meet, you can use features such as &amp;ldquo;Speaker ID&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Change Speakers,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Regenerate Meeting Summary&amp;rdquo; to reassign and replace the correct speakers in the meeting transcript, and regenerate corresponding summaries based on the new speakers.
Identifying Speakers #  Based on the actual number of meeting participants, you can use &amp;ldquo;Identify Speakers&amp;rdquo; to resplit the transcript and specify how many speakers to distinguish            During the speaker identification process, you can leave the meeting at any time and return to view the results when it&amp;rsquo;s complete       When identification is complete, you can see participants distinguished as different speakers (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
