<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SeaVoice Discord Bot on </title>
    <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SeaVoice Discord Bot on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:19:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/1-intro-discord-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/1-intro-discord-bot/</guid>
      <description>🐙 The SeaVoice Bot is a new speech-to-text and text-to-speech Discord integration brought to you by Seasalt.ai, a startup run by some of the world’s leading experts in deep speech recognition, neural speech synthesis, and natural language processing. 🐙
Invite SeaVoice Bot to Discord Server   Watch Video Demo #  Why We Developed SeaVoice Discord Bot? # SeaVoice is a voice intelligence bot that uses advanced AI technology to improve the Discord voice channel experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why SeaVoice STT &amp; TTS?</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/2-why-discord-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/2-why-discord-bot/</guid>
      <description>🎯 Cutting-edge Accuracy # Speech technology is our specialty. We create our own models in-house using state of the art deep learning neural network algorithms.
⏱️ Real-time Transcription &amp;amp; Synthesis # Real-time speed is essential when you&amp;rsquo;re dealing with live conversation. We guarantee you&amp;rsquo;ll never fall behind in a conversation because of slow transcription speeds.
📂 Downloadable Transcription &amp;amp; Audio Files # Not only can you watch your transcriptions in real-time, but you can download them and save them for future use!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/3-how-to-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/3-how-to-use/</guid>
      <description>✍️ Speech-to-Text # Transcribe Audio from Discord Voice Channels # /recognize [language] # /recognize [language] -&amp;gt; Bot joins the voice channel you&amp;rsquo;re currently in, and continues to listen and output transcription in real time to the chat channel. The bot will record and transcribe everyone in the voice channel. Transcriptions are output to the text channel where the initial slash command was entered. When the session ends, the bot will DM the session creator a final transcription file, an SRT-formatted transcript file (used for subtitles), and a link to a full audio download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/4-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/4-configuration/</guid>
      <description>SeaVoice offers customizable settings for both servers and individual users.
Note: If you update any settings, you must stop and re-start any active /recognize sessions before the new configurations are applied.
👥 Setting for Everyone in Server #  /server_config [live_transcript] [transcript_recipients] [transcript_style] [ignore_bots] [censor]
 Use the /server_config command to configure the settings for the current server that you are in. Only users with admin permissions in the server may use this command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language Support</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/5-language-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/5-language-support/</guid>
      <description>SeaVoice currently supports 12 languages. The English and Mandarin (Taiwan) models are our own in-house models trained from scratch; they are highly accurate and reliable. However, we&amp;rsquo;re always working on creating new language models and improving our existing ones. We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear which languages you&amp;rsquo;re most eager to use! All other languages are supported using a multilingual open source model as the base. The performance wasn&amp;rsquo;t great out of the box, so we integrated it into our own STT pipeline and tuned the model to improve the performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community &amp; Support</title>
      <link>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/6-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.seasalt.ai/seavoice/discord/6-community/</guid>
      <description>Official Discord Server # Join our official Discord server! We&amp;rsquo;d love to chat and find out how we can improve our bot. Our bot is in active development - please let us know if you find any bugs, have ideas for new features, or want to provide any feedback!
  Support us on Top.gg # Your comments and votes make SeaVoice easier to find for new users!
 Support SeaVoice # Love the SeaVoice Bot?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
